<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ChitYogSadhana</string>
    <string name="no_connection">There is a problem with your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="forgot_pass1">Enter your email address and we\'ll send you a confirmation email!</string>

    //What is Chit yog
    <string name="chit_yog">\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is based on ancient wisdom and time-tested methods that helps us to understand that until a holistic approach is followed, we will stay dis-connected from our Chit and keep suffering at every level\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana shows us how the coverings to our Chit are formed by our mind making wrong choices (called Pragya-aparadh in Sanskrit), which leads to a dis-connection between Mind, Body and Chit. \n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana tells us that whenever we are dis-connected from our Chit, problems will come our way. \n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is a process to remove these coverings one by one and bring harmony between Mind, Body and Chit. \n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is a pathway to connect to our pure consciousness and to overcome our ailments at all levels; physical, mental and emotional. \n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana empowers us to overcome these problems through our own efforts, rather than seeking help from others or looking to mask our problems with pills or potions. \n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana helps us remove the root cause of our suffering, layer by layer, by following simple, practical routines in our day to day life so we can enjoy the benefits of our own awareness.\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is path of action\n</string>


    //what is chit
    <string name="chit">Chit is a Sanskrit word meaning awareness or consciousness:\n\n
\u2022 True awareness or to be aware of \n\n
\u2022 To understand.\n\n
\u2022 To comprehend\n\n

       \n\n It is the core principle in all levels of progress in life, physical, mental and spiritual.\n\n
        \u2022 Chit is our true self.  \n\n
\u2022 Chit is our identity\n\n
\u2022 Chit caries all the memories that impact on our actions, thoughts and deeds. \n\n
\u2022 Chit is our protection from all sorts of problems; physical, mental or emotional.  \n\n

As long as we are connected to our Chit, we can keep ourselves away from any physical, mental and emotional problems.\n\n The moment we get dis-connected from our Chit, these problems start building.
This dis-connection starts when we make wrong choices through our actions, deeds and thoughts. These wrong choices create a covering over our Chit, dis-connecting us from our true, inner self. \n\n</string>

    //our aim
    <string name="aim">Chit Yog Sadhana is designed to  \n\n
        \u2022 Bring wellbeing, peace, calmness and freedom from ailments; \n\n
        \u2022 Enable us to reveal our inner core.\n\n
        \u2022 Help us realise pain and suffering are our own creation and we can correct them; \n\n
        \u2022 Enhance awareness that peace is inside us all; \n\n
        \u2022 Enable us to face the world with courage and honesty. \n\n
    </string>

    //how it works
    <string name="works">\u2022 You will complete a questionnaire to determine your physical, mental and emotional state.  \n\n
        \u2022 The result will determine your entry point to the programme. \n\n
        \u2022 Each stage of the programme will ask you to complete a number of tasks to enhance your health and connect to your Chit. \n\n
        \u2022 At each stage, your efforts will be monitored \n\n
        \u2022 On completion of a stage you will assesses how effectively you have incorporated these tasks into your life\n\n
       \t\t \u2022 If successful, the next stage will be opened for you. \n\n
       \t\t \u2022 If unsuccessful, you will repeat a section of the stage\n\n
        \u2022 There are 6 stages in this programme. Stages 1-3 are free. There is a small fee after this point to move deeper into the programme \n\n
        Each stage of this programme has its own power to remove the covering from our Chit so don’t rush. Until you are fully satisfied with the results from each stage, don’t move to the next because the result will elude you. If this process is followed sincerely and honestly, you will achieve success</string>


    //who needs it
    <string name="need">Anyone who is: \n\n
        \u2022 Suffering at emotional, physical or mental level; \n\n
        \u2022 Tired of trying everything only to find nothing worked; \n\n
        \u2022 Feeling empty inside; \n\n
        \u2022 Feeling dis-connected; \n\n
        \u2022 Seeking inner peace; \n\n
        \u2022 Wanting total wellness; \n\n
        \u2022 Wanting to have better relationships in life. \n\n
        \u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is for those who have tried various methods to overcome their issues, such as anxiety, stress, depression, panic attacks, paranoia, jealousy and hatred or physical problems from simple hay fever to severe
health problems by:\n
\u2022 Working in the gym/exercise;\n
\u2022 Following various diet/nutrition plans;\n
\u2022 Following various meditation techniques but failing to achieve the
desired results.\n\n
    \n\nIt is important that each component of this programme must be followed in the sequence it is explained. There are no short cuts and we advise you not to skip any sections of this programme as missing a step will not help you achieve the desired result.</string>


    //Level one intro
    <string name="one_intro">This stage of Chit Yog Sadhana comprises various daily routines to cleanse and strengthen your body, which builds the foundation for the next stage. Each action will strengthen your body and mind and prepare you to embark on the next stage of your journey, where you will burn the layers covering your Chit and make your way through the darkness of mental and emotional problems to the light at the end of the tunnel. \n\n
    You will follow these daily regimes for 30 days.\n
    </string>
    <string name="step1_1">1. Get up early</string>
    <string name="step1_1_detail">You should wake up between 5.00–5.30 am as this time is considered a time of pure consciousness (Brahma Muhurta). In Vedic philosophy, it is said that from 3.30am till sunrise it is easier to connect to your Chit as the coverings are less potent during this time and our Chit has the natural ability to move upwards towards its source.
\n\nThe qualities of the environment at this time are pure, calm, clear and vibrant so our mind is calm, clear and stable and has the ability to connect easily with the body.
\n\nOn a physical level waking up during this period provides more clarity, stability in thoughts and actions as well as more vitality and energy. </string>
    <string name="step1_2">2. Brush your teeth and scrape your tongue</string>
    <string name="step1_2_detail">You should brush your teeth and scrape your tongue as soon as you wake up.
\n\nHave you ever noticed the coating on your tongue when you wake up? This is a sure sign you are dis-connected from your Chit. If you don’t remove this coating within 3 minutes of waking up, it will be re-absorbed and create more coating on your Chit.
\n\nThe colour of the coating will give you an idea of the type of problems you have. A cream or brown coating is a sign you suffer from anxiety, worries, or fear. Those suffering from anger, frustration, jealously, hatred or stress will have a yellowish coating while a thick, white coating is a sign you suffer from depression or possessiveness.</string>
    <string name="step_1_3">3. Make a morning de-tox drink</string>
    <string name="step_1_3_detail">Make a drink first thing in the morning. To a glass of warm water add,\n
\u2022 ½ teaspoon of grated ginger\n
\u2022 ½ teaspoon of honey\n
\u2022 ½ teaspoon of lemon juice\n
\nThis helps to flush the toxins from the gut before they get re-absorbed. If you suffer from various emotional problems, you will always have a build-up of toxins in your gut and this helps to flush them out. If not, these toxins ultimately create another covering on your Chit</string>
    <string name="step_1_4">4. Nasya (nasal drops)</string>
    <string name="step_1_4_detail">Every morning, put three drops of warm, cold pressed black sesame oil in each nostril and massage around the eyes and nose three times.
\n\nWhen dis-connected from your Chit you tend to feel a lack of enthusiasm or lack of cheerfulness, don’t feel like talking to anyone or get irritated and impatient easily. These drops help to counter these emotions and help to remove the covering from your Chit.
\n\nHow to use: Put the dropper bottle in a container of hot water for 10-15 minutes until the bottle feels warm. Then tilt your head back and apply the drops to your nose.
</string>
    <string name="step_1_5">6. Avoid hot showers</string>
    <string name="step_1_5_detail">Another sure sign you are dis-connected from your Chit is a desire for a hot shower. The more dis-connected you feel, the hotter the shower but this is counter-productive. This heat affects the pituitary and pineal glands which impacts on the secretion of serotonin, making a person feel dull, heavy and lacking in enthusiasm.
\n\nTo know if your shower is too hot, check if the steam rises above your head. If it does, it is too hot. Also, when you finish the shower, if you have reddish skin, the shower was too hot.</string>
    <string name="step_1_6">5. Self-massage with warm oil</string>
    <string name="step_1_6_detail">Every morning, before your shower, massage your body with warmed, cold-pressed black sesame oil in upward circular motion.
\n\nIf you experience emotions such as anxiety, worries, fear or confusion, you will always have a stiff and tight body, your hands and feet will be cold and your skin, dry. If you suffer from anger, frustration, jealousy or hatred your body will always be hot with skin rashes and boils while if you feel greed, depression or suicidal thoughts you will always have a sluggish lymphatic system which stagnates your energy flow. All these symptoms are signs of how dis-connected you are from your Chit.
\n\nDaily massage helps to improve circulation and flush toxins from the lymphatic system, allowing bodily energy to flow more rhythmically.  </string>
    <string name="step_1_7">7. Deep breathing</string>
    <string name="step_1_7_detail">At least three times a day, pause and take 10-15 long, deep, slow breaths through the nose.
\n\nShallow breathing is an indicator you are dis-connected from your Chit, so this helps to provide more fresh oxygen, which brings more vitality, vigour and ability connect to your Chit. </string>
    <string name="step_1_8">8. Morning and evening walk</string>
    <string name="step_1_8_detail">Every day, go for a 30-minute walk; once at around 6.00 am. and again at 6.00 pm
\n\nThis helps to bring more vitality, vigour and alertness. It loosens the body, improves circulation, bring more
groundedness and stablises the immune system. Until or unless you are physically and mentally strong and stable you cannot achieve the goal to connect with your Chit. </string>

    
    // Level one hidden text visible to 50% result users only

    <string name="extra_1">If you are suffering from anger, frustration or jealousy. They are also effective for people suffering
from burning eyes or high blood pressure:</string>
    <string name="green_grass">1. Walk of the green grass</string>
     <string name="green_grass_detail">Every morning, while the dew is still on the grass, walk barefoot on the
grass for 5 minutes.
\nThis helps to bring more groundedness as well as providing more freshness, alertness and clarity to the mind which helps to overcome the thoughts of dullness, stress, anger and anxiety which are core elements
that keep us dis-connected from our Chit
     </string>
    
    <string name="pore_rose">2. Pure rose water soaked eye pads on eyes.</string>
    <string name="pore_rose_detail">Put eye pads soaked in pure rose water on both eyes and leave for one minute. Remove the pads and you’ll notice they are warm. Repeat this process three times. Finally, splash the eyes will normal water
\nIf you are dis-connected from your Chit you can have sore, red, dry and burning eyes and can feel tired every day. This regime helps to keep your eyes fresher and alert
</string>

    <string name="extra_2">If you are suffering from lack of enthusiasm or depression:</string>

    <string name="sun">1. Look at the rising sun</string>
    <string name="sun_detail">Every morning, while the sun is still on the horizon, look towards the rising sun
for 15 seconds and then close your eyes but keep facing the sun. You will notice dark red colour in front of your eyes. If you are dis-connected from your Chit you will see a dark hole in this red colour. The larger the hole, the more covering on your Chit.
\nPerform this every morning for 3 minutes. Once you start connecting to your Chit, you will notice those holes disappear and the colour in front of your eyes will become brighter red and without holes. The day you are connected to Chit and it is stable, that red layer will start turning a reddish, golden yellow.
\n\nNB: Never look at the sun if it is above the horizon, when the rays are white</string>

    <string name="gandoosh">2. Gandoosh</string>
    <string name="gandoosh_deatil">Once a week, prepare the following:\n
\u2022 1 tablespoon of sesame oil\n
\u2022 1 teaspoon of honey\n
\u2022 ½ teaspoon of black pepper\n
\u2022 ½ teaspoon of black salt\n\n

Hold in your mouth and move around for 3 minutes then spit and rinse with warm water.
\nWhen you are dis-connected from your Chit you will either have a dry mouth or excessive saliva and soreness in the back of throat. Sometimes, the gums can start bleeding. This regime will minimise this impact.</string>

    <!--//Level two intro -->
    <!--<string name=""-->

    //Level three intro
    <string name="three_intro">
        The phrase, “We are what we eat” is not just about what you eat but also includes how you eat as this also impacts on Chit, particularly things like:\n\n
\u2022 Technology\n
\u2022 Surroundings\n
\u2022 Our ways to eat\n
\u2022 Our thoughts at time of eating
\n\nThese factors are responsible for either creating more covering on our Chit and taking us further away from our Chit or helping us remove these coverings to connect us with our Chit and give us inner peace and wellness that lasts.
        For the next 30 days, avoid eating the following activities:\n\n
\u2022 Don’t eat your meal while watching TV\n
\u2022 Don’t eat while talking\n
\u2022 Don’t eat when emotionally upset\n
\u2022 Don’t eat on the run\n
\u2022 Don’t eat and drink together\n
\u2022 Don’t eat while on phone\n
\u2022 Don’t eat while playing on computers\n
\u2022 Don’t cook when emotionally upset, either sad, anxious or stressed, angry or frustrated\n
\u2022 Don’t have bad thoughts while eating\n
\u2022 Don’t just eat to fill your tummy\n
\u2022 Never eat food when standing. Must sit while eating.\n
    </string>


    //Level four intro
    <string name="four_intro">
        This stage is key to your wellness. One wonders I did everything in my life to overcome my problems:\n\n
\u2022 I follow the advice of my medical professionals\n
\u2022 I follow the advice of my religious guru\n
\u2022 Gone to religious place every day\n
\u2022 Made lots of changes to my diet\n
\u2022 Meditate for 1 hour every day\n
\u2022 Have become a vegan\n
\u2022 Chant mantras every day\n
\u2022 Wear sandalwood paste on my forehead\n
\u2022 Followed daily routines to improve my lifestyle\n
\nBut still my mental and emotional issues affect me.\n\n
Chit Yog Sadhana advises us superficial changes never help to take the covering off from our Chit alone with above unless out thoughts, our deeds, our interactions with others improve and get better. Our control of our desires, our control of our senses all impact on our mind and lead mind to make mistakes, make wrong choices, perceive things around us differently.
\n\nChit Yog Sadhana as this level helps one to identify are we slave of our mind or are we master of our mind? Be master of your mind and take the covering off your Chit.
\n\nChit Yog Sadhana helps is to achieve this in two steps:\n
    </string>

    //Level four sub intro
    <string name="four_step_1">
        \n\nWe all understand that our thoughts become our emotions and our emotions lead to our actions, which can either create a covering on our Chit or help to remove it, depending on the nature of the deed. Therefore, it is important to process these thoughts and emotions on a daily basis because if we don’t, they can create more coverings to our Chit.
\n\nWhen one goes to sleep and enters a sub-conscious state, these emotions become active. According to the qualities of these emotions, they leave an imprint on our body and nervous system. For example, if one has un-processed emotions of anxiety and worry, they can impact the body in this form. The result of this situation is that despite a person having 8 -10 hours’ sleep, rather than being in a state of relaxation, our body and nervous system remain in an active mode, so we wake up feeling exhausted and fatigued rather than rested and calm. We are all aware that sleep is when the body repairs itself from the wear and tear of daily living. If our body is in an active state during this time, the repair work does not take place, and slowly the body’s immune system can become affected.
\n\nTo prevent this process, it is very important that we process our thoughts on a daily basis. No matter how busy you are, before going to bed sit for 10 minutes to review the day. Close your eyes and ask yourself:
\u2022 Did I get angry today?\n
\u2022 Did I get jealous with someone?\n
\u2022 Did I have feelings of hatred today?\n
\u2022 Did I get frustrated today?\n
\u2022 Did I cheat on someone today?\n
\u2022 Did I steal anything today?\n
\u2022 Did I get nervous today?\n
\u2022 Have I spoke a lie today?\n
\u2022 Have I done anything which I am not supposed to do?\n
\u2022 Have I said something to my parents that could be hurtful?\n
\u2022 As I upset with my children today?\n
\u2022 Did I treat my employees badly today?\n
\u2022 Have I dealt with my work colleagues wrongly?\n\n
If the answer to any of the above if ‘Yes”
\u2022 Identify what was it\n
\u2022 Why it happened\n
\u2022 How I can avoid it\n
\u2022 How can I improve it for tomorrow?\n\n
Continue this practice for 15 days.</string>

    //Level four sub intro 2
    <string name="four_step_2">
        \n\n\u2022 Each evening, before bed, stand in front of a mirror\n
\u2022 Look into to your eyes\n
\u2022 Place you hand on you heart and ask yourself, “Have I done anything wrong today?\n
\u2022 Keep repeating this question for 5 minutes, looking into your eyes the whole time\n
\u2022 During this time, if you have to look away from your reflection (even for 1 second), stop the practice and sit quietly for 10 minutes.\n
\u2022 Ask yourself what thoughts came up that made you look away. Were you remembering thoughts and actions that occurred during the day that made you uncomfortable? If so, make a commitment to yourself, to your Chit, not to repeat these thoughts and actions tomorrow. If you realise you have reacted the wrong way in a situation, identify it and make a commitment to amend your behaviour for next time. Also, make a commitment to apologise to anyone you may have hurt next time you see them.\n
\u2022 Repeat this process every night until you are able to look into the mirror for the full five minutes without looking away.\n
\nThose who can do this on a daily basis can rest assured that though they might suffer from some physical problem in their life, they will never ever suffer from any mental ailments.\n
\nWhen ready, you can move onto the next stage</string>

    <string name="intro_two">There is a saying, “We are what we eat”. Our thoughts and actions are influenced by the food we eat so we need to minimise the intake of foods which can cause more covering to our Chit. When we are dis-connected from our Chit we begin to make wrong choices we have to take wrong decisions which leads to do such activity which can build another layer on our Chit.
\n\nFor the next 30 days, avoid eating the following foods:
\n\nFrozen food:
        \n\t\tFrozen food is considered more dull, heavy and difficult to digest. This food has natural tendency to make one’s mind duller heavy and cloudy which makes it difficult for one to work to re-connect to their Chit and connect with it hence it is advisable to avoid all frozen food
        \n\nTinned food:
        \n\t\tThis food also lacks prana life force which is very essential to make connections with Chit. Hence those who have dis-connected from Chit always naturally go towards liking tinned foods but those seeking to connect with Chit should avoid eating tinned food
        \n\nProcessed food:
        \n\t\tStimulating – Creates more disharmony with Chit
        \n\nMicrowaved food:
        \n\t\tLacks Prana – Creates confusion with Chit
        \n\nWhite bread:
        \n\t\tHeavy, dull, sticky -  Creates heaviness and dullness, lack of energ.
        \n\nCoffee:
        \n\t\tStimulating – Creates more dis-harmony. Burns Prana
        \n\nPeanut Butter:
        \n\t\tHeavy, oily - Creates more disharmony with Chit
        \n\nChilli:
        \n\t\tHot: Creates more disharmony with Chit. Burns Prana
        \n\nWhite sugar:
        \n\t\tBring more aggravation
        \n\nTomato sauce:
        \n\t\tAcidic, heavy; Disharmony with Chit. Burns Prana
        \n\nAlcohol:
        \n\t\tStimulating. Disconnect with Chit lead to making wrong choices
        \n\nMarijuana:
        \n\t\tMind altering. Disconnect with Chit
        \n\nRecreational drugs:
        \n\t\tBuild more covering on Chit by making wrong choices
        \n\nPre-cooked foods:
        \n\t\tCloudy, heavy and dull
        \n\nRed meat:
        \n\t\tHeavy, dull, cloudy and dead food (lacks Prana). Adds more layers
        \n\nChilli sauce:
        \n\t\tStimulating\n

    </string>


    <string name="step_five">\u2022 You are almost there.\n\n
\u2022 You are knocking at the door that will take you to connect to you Chit.\n\n
\u2022 Through this process of Chit Yog Sadhana you will be able to burn the layers faster and forever.\n\n
\u2022 Complete the questionnaire below and you will get x2 guided techniques.\n\n
\u2022 Follow them and the door will open!\n\n
      \nSelect one of the emotional states below that best represents how you feel most of the time: (Client
can only select one variable) \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="step_5_1">
      \u2022 Anxiety, worries, fear or panic attacks? depression
    </string>
    <string name="step_5_2">
     \u2022 Rejection, lack of respect, taken for granted, feeling used, being abused, childhood abuse
    </string>
    <string name="step_5_3">
    \u2022 Sensitivity, holding emotions, inability to express yourself, suppressed emotions and depression
    </string>
    <string name="step_5_4">
     \u2022 Stress, anger, frustration, jealousy and hatred?
    </string>


    <string name="p1_52">\u2022 Sit in a comfortable position and in a quiet place. (Never use your bedroom for meditation!)
    \n\u2022 Place a picture of someone who you respect, like and admire or feel connected with. It can either be you mother, father, teacher, guru or any other individual to whom you feel connected. This should be a person, not a picture of nature.
    \n\u2022 Keep looking at the picture.
    \n\u2022 Look into the eyes of the picture.
   \n\u2022 Bring your focus to that level that you start only seeing the picture and the room goes dark.
    \n\u2022 Maintain deep breathing.
    \n\u2022 Continue in this state for 15 minutes.\n\n
    You should do this first stage for at least 15 days.
    \n\nHow to identify you are ready for the next stage of clinical guided meditation?\n When you start seeing the eyes in the picture and nothing of your surroundings and can maintain this for 15 minutes you are ready to go the next stage, which is closed eye candle meditation.\n\n
   </string>

    <string name="p2_52">
        \u2022 Sit in a comfortable position and in a quiet place. (Never use your bedroom for meditation!)
\n\u2022 Place a lighted candle at an arm’s length at eye level.
\n\u2022 Focus your attention on the lighted candle for 15 seconds and then close your eyes.
\n\u2022 Visualise the image of the lighted candle on your third eye and try to keep your concentration around that light.
\n\u2022 After few seconds, you might notice the flame is gone. If this happens, open your eyes again, look at the flame for 10 seconds and repeat the visualisation.
\n\u2022 Keep this practice going until the image of the lighted candle stops flickering and becomes more stable and remains there for the time of meditation for a minimum of 20 minutes.
\n\u2022 Repeat this meditation every day without much expectation and monitor your progress.
\n\u2022 Once you are able to keep the flame at 3rd eye for 20 minutes, you can go to the last stage of Chit Yog.\n\n
NB: Make sure you blow out the candle when finished\n\n
You should do this first stage for at least 15 days.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="p1_51">\u2022 Sit in a comfortable position and in a quiet place. (Never use your bedroom for meditation!)
\n\u2022 Put a lighted candle at arms length at eye level.
\n\u2022 Start looking at the flame. You don’t need to think of anything. Just focus on the flame.
\n\u2022 Keep looking at the flame (during this period you can blink your eyes).
\n\u2022 Maintain deep breathing.
\n\u2022 Do this for 15 minutes.
\n\u2022 Do this every day, at the same time and in the same place.
\n\nNB: Make sure you blow out the candle when finished\n\n
You should do this first stage for at least 15 days.\n\n
How to identify you are ready for the next stage of clinical guided meditation?\n When you start seeing the flame of candle in the room and nothing of your surroundings and can maintain this for 15 minutes you are ready to go the next stage, which is closed eye candle meditation.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="p2_51">
        \u2022 Sit in a comfortable position and in a quiet place. (Never use your bedroom for meditation!)
\n\u2022 Place a lighted candle at an arm’s length at eye level.
\n\u2022 Focus your attention on the lighted candle for 15 seconds and then close your eyes.
\n\u2022 Visualise the image of the lighted candle on your third eye and try to keep your concentration around that light.
\n\u2022 After few seconds, you might notice the flame is gone. If this happens, open your eyes again, look at the flame for 10 seconds and repeat the visualisation.
\n\u2022 Keep this practice going until the image of the lighted candle stops flickering and becomes more stable and remains there for the time of meditation for a minimum of 20 minutes.
\n\u2022 Repeat this meditation every day without much expectation and monitor your progress.
\n\u2022 Once you are able to keep the flame at 3rd eye for 20 minutes, you can go to the last stage of Chit Yog.
\n\nNB: Make sure you blow out the candle when finished\n\n
You should do this first stage for at least 15 days.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="p1_53">
        \u2022 Sit in a comfortable position and in a quiet place. (Never use your bedroom for meditation!)
        \n\u2022 Start chanting word, “OM” (Om is the universal sound, known as the 1st sound that manifest from the un-manifested state. The vibration of this word helps energy to flow in the body and helps to take the covering from you Chit).
\n\u2022 Do for 20 minutes daily.
\n\u2022 You should do this first stage for at least 15 days\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="p2_53">\u2022 Sit in a comfortable position and in a quiet place. (Never use your bedroom for meditation!)
\n\u2022 Place a lighted candle at an arm’s length at eye level.
\n\u2022 Focus your attention on the lighted candle for 15 seconds and then close your eyes.
\n\u2022 Visualise the image of the lighted candle on your third eye and try to keep your concentration around that light.
\n\u2022 After few seconds, you might notice the flame is gone. If this happens, open your eyes again, look at the flame for 10 seconds and repeat the visualisation.
\n\u2022 Keep this practice going until the image of the lighted candle stops flickering and becomes more stable and remains there for the time of meditation for a minimum of 20 minutes.
\n\u2022 Repeat this meditation every day without much expectation and monitor your progress.
\n\u2022 Once you are able to keep the flame at 3rd eye for 20 minutes, you can go to the last stage of Chit Yog.
\n\nNB: Make sure you blow out the candle when finished\n\n
You should do this first stage for at least 15 days.\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="p1_54">This form of meditation is good for people suffering from stress, anger, aggression, jealousy and hatred. In this meditation, you need to use light music to build on the ability to concentrate.
 \n\n\u2022 Sit in a comfortable position and in a quiet place. (Never use your bedroom for meditation!)
 \n\u2022 Count your pulse rate as you begin.
 \n\u2022 Play light soothing music
 \n\u2022 Keep listening to the music for 20 minutes
 \n\u2022 Now count your pulse rate. If it has come down by at least 10 beats per minute the meditation has worked.
 \n\u2022 You can now go the next stage.
 \n\u2022 You might experience some dry tears in your eyes. This is a normal sign.\n\n
You should do this first stage for at least 15 days.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="p2_54">
        \u2022 Sit in a comfortable position and in a quiet place. (Never use your bedroom for meditation!)
\n\u2022 Place a lighted candle at an arm’s length at eye level.
\n\u2022 Focus your attention on the lighted candle for 15 seconds and then close your eyes.
\n\u2022 Visualise the image of the lighted candle on your third eye and try to keep your concentration around that light.
\n\u2022 After few seconds, you might notice the flame is gone. If this happens, open your eyes again, look at the flame for 10 seconds and repeat the visualisation.
\n\u2022 Keep this practice going until the image of the lighted candle stops flickering and becomes more stable and remains there for the time of meditation for a minimum of 20 minutes.
\n\u2022 Repeat this meditation every day without much expectation and monitor your progress.
\n\u2022 Once you are able to keep the flame at 3rd eye for 20 minutes, you can go to the last stage of Chit Yog.
\n\nNB: Make sure you blow out the candle when finished\n\n
You should do this first stage for at least 15 days.\n\n


    </string>
    
    <string name="six_intro">
        Congratulations.
\n\nYou have completed each stage of this programme to connect to your Chit. I am sure you have experienced lots of changes at the physical, mental and emotional levels and that you feel more energetic and focused. You have better interactions with people around you and your thoughts are more positive. These are indications that the covering over your Chit has broken.
\nTo make this experience last, we recommend you keep following all these regimes to the best of your ability as this is the only way to keep ourselves in a stable state in this world.
\nHowever, if you are ready to fully connect to your Chit, then purchase the final stage of Chit Yog Sadhana so you can experience total bliss at the physical, mental and emotional levels.
\n\nOn receipt of your payment you will receive:
\n\u2022 a personalised mantra and instructions on how to use this in your meditation practice;
\n\u2022  an ancient elixir, used by yogis for centuries to enhance their meditation practice.
\n\nDo you want to proceed to the final stage: Yes/No?
    </string>
</resources>
