<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ChitYogSadana</string>
    <string name="no_connection">There is a problem with your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="forgot_pass1">Enter your email address and we\'ll send you a confirmation email!</string>

    //What is Chit yog
    <string name="chit_yog">\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is a process to understand why and how we suffer from various imbalances at every level; physical, mental and emotional.\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana tells us that whenever one is dis-connected from their Chit, problems will come their way.\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is a pathway to connect to your pure consciousness to overcome one’s ailments at all levels; physical, mental and emotional.\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is for those who have tried various methods to overcome their issues, such as anxiety, stress, depression, panic attacks, paranoia, jealousy and hatred, either by:\n
       \t\t\t \u25BA Working in the gym;\n

       \t\t\t \u25BA Following various diet;\n

       \t\t\t \u25BA Following various meditation techniques.\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is based on ancient wisdom and time-tested methods that prove that until a complete approach of purification is followed, coverings from our Chit will not be removed and we will stay dis-connected and keep suffering at every level.\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana helps in all kinds of issues such as depression, anxiety stress, panic attacks, paranoia jealousy, hatred and physical problems\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana empowers an individual to overcome their problems with their own efforts, rather than seeking help or guidance from others or looking to mask their symptoms with pills or potions.\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana helps an individual remove the root cause of their suffering, layer by layer, by following simple, practical routines in their day to day life so they can enjoy the benefits of their own awareness.\n\n
\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is path of action\n</string>


    //what is chit
    <string name="chit">\u2022 Chit is our true self.\n\n
\u2022 It is our pure consciousness.\n\n
\u2022 Chit is one’s identity.\n\n
\u2022 Chit caries all the memories that impact on our actions, thoughts and deeds.\n\n
\u2022 Chit is our true awareness.\n\n
\u2022 Chit is our protection from all sorts of problems; physical, mental or
emotional.\n\n
As long as one is connected to his/her Chit, they are protected and able to keep themselves away from any physical, mental and emotional problems. The moment one gets dis-connected from their Chit, problems start building.\n\n
This dis-connection starts when we make wrong choices through our actions, deeds and thoughts. These wrong choices create a covering over our Chit, dis-connection us from our true self.\n\n</string>

    //our aim
    <string name="aim">Aim of Chit Yog Sadhana is to\n\n
        \u2022 Bring wellbeing, peace, calmness and freedom from ailments.\n\n
        \u2022 Enable everyone to reveal their inner core.\n\n
        \u2022 Helps us realise pain and suffering are our own creation and we have the
ability to correct them\n\n
        \u2022 Enhance awareness that peace is inside everyone\n\n
        \u2022 Enable everyone to face the world with courage and honesty\n\n
    </string>

    //how it works
    <string name="need">\u2022 Those who are suffering at emotional, physical or mental level;\n\n
        \u2022 Those who are tried everything and it did not work;\n\n
        \u2022 Those who feel empty inside;\n\n
        \u2022 Those who feel dis-connected;\n\n
        \u2022 Those who are seeking inner peace;\n\n
        \u2022 Those who want total wellness;\n\n
        \u2022 Those who don’t want to mask their symptoms;\n\n
        \u2022 Those who want to have better relationships in life.\n\n
        Each of us need to understand we are responsible for our own state of health. Unless we amend our actions, we will not be able to move forward.\n\n
        Chit Yog Whatever problems we suffer from cannot be resolved by a fragmented approach so each component of this programme needs to be followed. Those who feel there is an easy way out or think they can skip sections of this programme and achieve the desired result, then this path is not for you.\n\n
        Chit Yog Sadhana is process if followed sincerely, honestly and with commitment, will achieve success for you.</string>


    //who needs it
    <string name="works">\u2022 Chit Yog Sadhana is a practical path to achieve success.\n\n
        \u2022 You will complete a questionnaire to determine your physical, mental and
emotional state. The result will determine your entry point to the
programme.\n\n
        \u2022 Each stage of the programme will ask you to complete a number of tasks to
enhance your health and connect you to your Chit.\n\n
        \u2022 At each stage, your efforts will be monitored\n\n
        \u2022 At the conclusion of the stage you will assesses how sincerely and effectively you have incorporated these tasks into your life.\n\n
        \u2022 If successful, the next stage will be opened for you.\n\n
        \u2022 If unsuccessful, you will repeat a section of the stage.\n\n
        \u2022 There are 6 stages in this programme. Stages 1-3 are free. There is a small fee after this point as you move deeper into the programme\n\n
        \u2022 Every stage of this programme has its own importance and power to remove the covering from one’s Chit so until you are fully satisfied with the result at each stage and are able to incorporate them into your life, don’t move to next stage because the result will elude you. Then you will say Chit Yog Sadhana does not work when in fact it is you who need to reflect on your actions.\n\n</string>


    //Level one intro
    <string name="one_intro">The first stage of Chit Yog Sadhana is various routines to cleanse the system and build the foundation for the next stage. Each action of this stage will strengthen every individual to take up the next part of the journey, where one will burn the layers covering their Chit and make their way through the darkness of mental and emotional problems to see the light at the end of the tunnel.
\n\nYou will follow these daily regimes for 30 days.</string>
    <string name="step1_1">1. Get up early</string>
    <string name="step1_1_detail">It is advisable for you wake up between 5.00 – 5.30 am as this time is considered as pure consciousness time (Brahma Muhurta). In Vedic philosophy, it is said that from 3.30am till sunrise one has more ability to connect with their Chit as the coverings are less potent during this period and one’s Chit has the natural ability to move upwards towards its source.
\nAt this time, the qualities of the environment are pure, calm, clear and vibrant so one’s mind is calm, clear and stable and has the ability to connect with the body easily.
\nOn physical level waking up during this period provides more clarity, stability in thoughts.</string>
    <string name="step1_2">2. Brush your teeth and scrape your tongue</string>
    <string name="step1_2_detail">Those who are dis-connected from their Chit or have lots of covering on their Chit will find their tongues will always have a coating in the morning when they wake up.
\nThe colour of the coating will be based on the type of emotions one suffers from. Those suffering from anxiety, worries, fear will have light white, brown coating on their tongue. Those suffering from anger, frustration, jealously, hatred, stress will have a coating of white-yellow colour. Those suffering from depression, possessiveness, greed, sadness will have white thick costing on their tongue.
\nIf one does not remove this coating within 3 minutes of waking up the coating will be re-absorbed and create more coating on their Chit. Hence it is advisable to brush teeth and scrape tongue within 3 minutes of getting up.</string>
    <string name="step_1_3">3. Make a morning de-tox drink</string>
    <string name="step_1_3_detail">Make a drink first thing in the morning. To a glass of warm water add,\n
\u2022 ½ teaspoon of grated ginger\n
\u2022 ½ teaspoon of honey\n
\u2022 ½ teaspoon of lemon juice\n
\nThis helps to flush the toxins from the gut before they get re-absorbed. Those who suffer from various emotions will always has a build-up of toxins in their gut and this helps to flush them out. If not, these toxins ultimately create another covering on their Chit and a stronger dis-connection from their Chit.</string>
    <string name="step_1_4">4. Nasya (nasal drops)</string>
    <string name="step_1_4_detail">Everyone should put three drops of warm, cold pressed black sesame oil in each nostril and massage around the eyes and nose three times.
\nThose who are dis-connected from their Chit always tend to experience a lack of enthusiasm or lack of cheerfulness. Sometime don’t feel like talking to anyone or get irritated and impatient easily. They tend to get angry or frustrated very easily.
\nThese drops help to counter these emotions and help to remove the covering from their Chit.</string>
    <string name="step_1_5">5. Avoid hot showers</string>
    <string name="step_1_5_detail">Those who are dis-connected from their Chit always like hot showers. The more dis-connected, the hotter the shower but this can be counter-productive. This heat affects the pituitary and pineal glands which impacts on the secretion of serotonin, making a person feel dull, heavy and lacking in enthusiasm.
\nTo know if your shower is too hot, check if the steam rises above your head. If it does, it is too hot. Also, when you finish the shower, if you have red/pink skin, the shower was too hot.</string>
    <string name="step_1_6">6. Self-massage with warm oil</string>
    <string name="step_1_6_detail">Those suffering from emotions such as anxiety, worries, fear, confusion will always have stiff and tight bodies, their hand and feet will always be cold and their skin dry.
\nThose suffering from anger, frustration, jealously hatred their bodies will always be hot with skin rashes and boils.
\nThose suffering from greed, passiveness, depression, suicidal thoughts will always have sluggish lymphatic system their bodies will have a natural tendency to hold water. This also stagnates your energy flow.
\nAll these are a sign of how you are dis-connected from your Chit.
\nEvery morning, before your shower, one should massage their body with warmed, cold-pressed black sesame oil in upward circular motion. It helps to improve lymphatic and circulation systems and flush toxins from lymphatic system and improve the immune system. This massage also makes bodily energy flow more rhythmically. </string>
    <string name="step_1_7">7. Deep breathing</string>
    <string name="step_1_7_detail">Shallow breathing is an indicator you are dis-connected from your Chit.
\nEveryone must take 10-15 long, deep, slow breaths through the nose three times a day. This helps to provide fresh prana to one’s body which brings more vitality, vigour and ability connect to one’s Chit.</string>
    <string name="step_1_8">8. Morning and evening walk</string>
    <string name="step_1_8_detail">One must go for a 30 minute walk every day around 6.00am. and again at 6.00 pm This helps to bring more vitality, vigour and alertness. It loosens the body, improves circulation, bring more groundedness and stablises the immune system.
\nUntil or unless one is physically and mentally strong and stable one cannot make effort to connect with his/her Chit.</string>


    <!--//Level two intro -->
    <!--<string name=""-->

    <string name="intro_two">There is a saying, “We are what we eat”. Our thoughts and actions are influenced by the food we eat so we need to minimise the intake of foods which can cause more covering to our Chit. When we are dis-connected from our Chit we begin to make wrong choices we have to take wrong decisions which leads to do such activity which can build another layer on our Chit.
\n\nFor the next 30 days, avoid eating the following foods:</string>


</resources>
